gatorcountry.com 2002-06-05

# Gator Country - FLORIDA GATORS - GATORCOUNTRY.COM -- The #1 Florida Gator fan site since 1996!

|  | 

Main Menu  
  
---|---  
| 

Home Page  
News & Columns  
GC Chat Room  
FREE GatorNews  
Gator Sports Events  
Gator Baseball  
Gator Manuel Radio  
GC Links  
GC Greeting Cards  
Top 10 Stats  
Submit News & More  
  
Advertise on GC!  
  
Privacy Statement  
Entire Site Map  

| 

GET YOUR FAN GEAR!  
  
| 

| 

SPONSOR GATOR COUNTRY!  
  
| 

Get the most out of your sales - advertise on Gator Country! Interested? Click here!  
  
|   
| 

| 

GatorInsider  
  
| 

[Exclusive Interview with Anaheim Angels Shortstop David Eckstein](http://www.gatorinsider.com/article.php?sid=757)

| 

LATEST...FORUM...POSTS  
  
| 

| 

LATEST..GC..AUCTIONS  
  
| 

|   
|  | 

### Privacy Statement for Gator Country

Gator Country has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. **Gator Country** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

This site, Gator Country, uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>. 

We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). Third Party Cookies In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Only the owners of Gator Country (Ray Hines), have access to any and all information on Gator Country's servers, and they will not allow anyone else to have access to this data.

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [gators@gatorcountry.org](mailto:gators@gatorcountry.org)

### Change/Modify

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [gators@gatorcountry.org](mailto:gators@gatorcountry.org)

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Raymond Hines gators@gatorcountry.org

|
